<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-27T11:56:04-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">AAE (Another Arcade Emulator)</title><subtitle>AAE is a primarily vector based arcade system emulator/simulator written using C and OpenGL.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Coming Soon in 2023: The “If You Can’t Beat Em, Copy Em“ release.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/update/2023/01/25/coming-soon-update.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Coming Soon in 2023: The “If You Can’t Beat Em, Copy Em“ release." /><published>2023-01-25T12:28:34-05:00</published><updated>2023-01-25T12:28:34-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/update/2023/01/25/coming-soon-update</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/update/2023/01/25/coming-soon-update.html"><![CDATA[<div class="row">
  <div class="column almostHalfWidth">
  <img src="../../../../assets/img/Main Menu.jpg" alt="Main Menu" class="fullSize screenShot" />
  </div>
  <div class="column almostHalfWidth floatingRight">
  <img src="../../../../assets/img/Game Key Config.jpg" alt="Game Key Config" class="fullSize screenShot" />
  </div>
</div>
<p class="centerText">Where have I seen this input menu before?</p>
<p><br /></p>

<p>I can’t believe it’s been 15 years since the last release. I actually never stopped working on AAE, over the years I made major changes, added new C++ cpu cores, accurate timing,  incorporated MAME’s ™ more accurate Atari vector engine, and slowly worked toward a release. But then I looked back on it, and basically what I had done was make a straight ripoff of Mame. This isn’t quite what I had in mind when I started this, so into the dustbin it went.
In 2022 I found myself with some free time on my hands, so I went back to the original code and took a look at it.
Many weeks later what I have is a cleaned up version of the last release, with an updated and slightly overhauled artwork backend, I also up-ported and incorporated the input system right out of MAME circa .33 to .72 versions. This blatant code copy gives many much needed fixes to all the drivers, bringing proper input and dipswitch handling to all games, including analog input to tailgunner.  Many sound fixes have been ported from MAME as well for the Cinematronics games, and while it’s still compiled 32bit because of the assembly 68000 engine it works fine in Windows 10/11.</p>

<p>Watch this space for more news. Thanks!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where have I seen this input menu before?]]></summary></entry></feed>